Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is alright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Whoa
Hearts and the balance
Every card an open door
Feel the romance
I'll be right with you. Let me see. Okay. Oh, shit. That's all. Okay. Open. I have a new song.
We'll see how it goes.
I'll put the new song up. Okay. Here it comes. Try another video too.
Let me see.
Try this one.
How are you guys doing today?
Hope you guys are all good.
Let's see.
Uh-oh, not Google Drive.
I'm going to go Add File, Choose Files.
Actually, it is Google Drive.
OK, I'll try this one, too.
See if this one works.
OK, how are you guys?
Let me see.
Hey, everybody.
13 people.
You like the new songs?
What's wild with the AI pics?
These are just, well, what am I going wild on my,
oh shit, on my community page?
I'll use a few.
But they're actually there,
because my picture is just kind of
I've put in outfits and stuff.
We get to 25 people, I will play the new song.
But let me see how this is working.
I think I have the de-high thing downloading.
Let me see, is it working?
Okay, the song's ready,
but I'm gonna try another de-high thing.
Let me see.
Let's see, add choose files.
Okay.
This core shocker.
I don't know if I have this one downloaded.
Let's see if it's working.
Okay.
Well, 25 people. Hey, what's up guys? How are we doing today? Let's see sassy. Halo KZ reality Nancy J dog
Halo the god Vicky. Hey guys
Hey, those Samantha Avery, thank you for being here KZ. How you get everybody? Hey guys
Well, you know work on it work on it
easy. That thing's impossible, right? I think I've done that a few times. Oh, it's
working now. It's working now. Okay, so we'll see how this goes and then we'll
see the song. 25 people in the chat will start the song. Everybody maybe share
the live. I have the new hashtags I'm using too.
I'm doing pretty good today.
You know, I had a, I have a really good dinner last night.
It was really good.
I got these lamb euros, your G-Y-R-O-S, right?
They're really good, really good.
Okay, so this is not working, I guess.
Let's try one more time.
It keeps going like sideways, like, you know, when I try it,
I just have to wait while I'm sideways for one second.
I think it should work, but it will go sideways probably.
Guys, also I cleared out my ear,
I got this like really crazy,
I know it's kinda gross, but it's like this camera,
it was like 12, 13 bucks,
because I had my, I couldn't hear out of my ear
because I was like using Q-tips
and it's like I clogged my whole ear, right?
So it's kinda gross, right?
But then I got this camera thing.
And it's like this little camera and it's like you put it up to your to your
Wi-Fi and then he's like you put on the app and then it's like it sees like you go inside your ear
My ear is so gross. It's like all hairy inside and then I just saw like this disgusting like it was just impacted
It was like disgusting and dug it out for a while
They just took a bath and like got it all hot and stuff and it's like I kind of like I did for the first time in like a week
My ear cleared out
Now my other one clogged up again. I need to like work on the other one now. I know it's like I'm half-deaf right now
It's like it's fun crazy, but
The good news is that you know my ears are my ears are clean
So that's some good news and it also came up with all these other tools like this is it comes with these like little tools
And you're just like but I guess you're these all attached to the camera. You're supposed to like figure out through the camera like where to go
It's crazy. It's crazy stuff
Okay, when we get 25 people in here, I'll I'll I'll premiere the new song
Just let everyone know that we're live. Okay, so here's the third D high man. What are you doing?
I'm sitting here. I'm sitting here looking at you in a state of shock
What in a state of shock is watching you why did you see your discord?
You're just my discord
Oh, no, I made a discord. I didn't even remember.
Remember when you sent me that picture of a gerbil?
Call, you remember that?
Call.
Remember I asked you for new,
so for your new photos and you sent me a picture
of South Park.
South Park, yeah.
Lemuees, the gerbil from South Park, yeah.
That wasn't a, that wasn't a new photo.
Right, that was a good one.
It wasn't a good it wasn't I know that was a good episode
But it didn't make any sense for what I asked and then you sent me a picture of a giant cartoon gerbil
He asked for nerds and so I just see you there in sir side of my asshole. Oh my god
I'm so happy I was hoping that wasn't the joke
Oh
Wow. Oh gosh. That's pretty funny. Okay, let me get my letter. Oh, I know we need to get some old people over here before like Arthur comes in and says, where was everybody? Where is everybody? And I'm sorry, guys, I was on it like three in the morning. And I had a great panel. I had like seven people on the panel. We had Crystal Marie. We had, we had a bunch of people here. We had this guy, Revila Red. We had
JT for a little bit. We just had a bunch of people here. It was fun
And then I think the people start someone came on and their name. I'll tell you their name
It was like it was a guy's name
But then when you clicked on the name it said Amanda hugging kiss. So I was like, okay, that seems like it's gonna be a
Porn bomb or some a n-word bomb, you know, well if they can't form on me this n-word bomb, right?
so
And then he was like sitting there and then he's backstage and he was like, oh, I want to read you
Can I I would please just I just want to read you real quick and I was like, yeah, I've heard that before too
And I was like, but then I get like I get tired of like
Seeing them backstage and it's like we'll make us like maybe there's like a 1% chance like if someone needs help
I'll do 1% chance and maybe like help me somebody
And I would switch over and then it was the n-word n-word n-word n-word n-word n-word
It sounded like Tony's voice again, you know, he just that's all that's all he does
It's like, you know, and if you can't just regular bomb and we're bomb if he doesn't get on me like yeah
It's just I sounded like him
He like he really does like to do the poor mom better because he knows the n-word doesn't really do anything
It just kind of bothers me because I don't like first. I don't like the word and second of all
So, I, you know, just ended the show and went to bed.
It sucks that people will do that.
And it's like, they think it's, I mean, it's like the same person.
That's basically not a lot of people that think it's the same person.
It probably does it to like a lot of people in other shows.
We're almost at the 20, well, I'll do it at 20 people.
I'll play the song.
I'll replay it and maybe like, then there's more people.
So, yeah, it was kind of like, it was kind of sucky.
Because we were having a good conversation like okay, let's bring people into it
And then there's just people that are like people just sit around waiting for me to go live so they can try to plumb all this shit like that
So I think next time it's like somebody that I don't know comes here. It's like oh, I want to come on the panel and
This will be controversial that pills feel you're charging people look on the panel
I'm gonna start charging people. I don't know with no camera on and like some weird name
I'll say okay if you want to read on the panel
Send five bucks or more
Then I'll let you on the panel
Just have somebody I don't know that it's just expected for bomber. I'll just do that
Is there anything wrong with that? I don't think so because it's like yo first of all
They're asking something for me
They're asking for a service and I can do it for free if they're in the chat
Now I'll do it for free some somebody I know familiar with for sure, but
If there's like some random person that gets here and like just wants to come on piano and then it puts me my show at risk and
It has has all my donations that I mean is everything that risk if I like let people up sometimes
Then you know they can like throw a few bucks at me and then maybe I'll know they're legitimate
If not, I'll have to end the show anyway
But I got a few bucks
So that's gonna be the way I'm gonna deal with that from now on. I think it's a pretty good idea
By the way, how much is lifetime ban on?
Brutal hmm
Make a make a author
You make an offer
Yeah
You know if it's like
You know Birdo is not the most important person on the show, right several hundreds. Yeah, you think so I
Mean I would say several hundred if it's like, you know a
Friend of the show, you know, but it's like in some people I probably wouldn't even take I would like just refuse, you know
But I don't know he's not I mean it's like I've let him on the air recently and stuff
I don't think they're a bad person, but you know if you want to make an offer
Go ahead and make an offer
We have 20 people in the chat. Let's play the new song. So here's the new song. I've never, I haven't listened to it yet. I just, you know, put the concepts through. So, see if you like the song, guys, okay?
Well, Psyche's in his Speedos, Stars and Stripes Parade
Fish taco's on the table, Another wild charade
He's hitting on the straight men, Come on, lose that shirt
Meanwhile, Beta's on the hotline, Yelling till it hurts
Pretty pages dodging simps, Like dodgeball in the gym
Canada drag got gonged off
Christine's with fozzy bear
Arthur's stirring pots like he's cooking up a scare
Trucker rattle rumbles in salmon's chasing views dj electros cartoon face spray
Spirits here in every man
No, that was cute, huh? Hi, Empress Janet
You loved it. Okay good. I need to put you know, I
Had to think about the things I put in it
But I need to make some more with others the other jokes and stuff like that, you know
but that was like kind of like a
soon the a
As soon as the end will be said without repercussion. Hmm. I don't know about that. I
Don't know about that one interesting theory
Hi Janet, what's up guys? Oh, oh, hold on. I'll get my thing off. Oh, that was a cute little country song though
It was supposed to be like a whimsical
whimsical folk song
There we go. Hi guys
How am I telling the piece today? Hey, time. How are you Janet? What's up?
Let me get the let's have a free day. So what's a Saturday? Let's do a free a free
Free day here on up everybody since I had to end the panel early this morning. I was doing a free morning
I mean, it's like I do mostly
free paddles
occasionally
And they get a little bit much from me.
I'm on a tight.
I hope you're having a wonderful day too, sweetheart.
Yeah, so the chat GPT is now on chat GPT5.
And it's just, I noticed it was a little smarter.
It's actually like a little bit,
it knows some kind of questions
that I maybe want the answers to.
And so I learned some cool things
and got some good ideas.
Okay. Oh, yeah, green. I like green on jet. Okay. So let's see. Let's do a collective reading.
And if you'd like a reading, free reading, let me know.
I'll put the link up here. If you'd like a free reading, let me know.
If you'd like a paid reading on the panel or through the chat, you know, I can put up my banner.
But I'm also happy to do free if you'd like here's a collective and people to say I don't shuffle I do shuffle
I guess maybe don't shuffle like a Vegas person, but
It's shuffling
I need to maybe work on my shuffle and like have a little bit more dramatic flair to it, but it works for me
I mean, it's like oh, you're not show me. You're just picking out the cards
No, I'm not the cards are face down. Do you see how they're face down like I can't really kick them in their face down unless they
Could see through them. I really can't
Okay
Good to see you to he man
Okay, guys, look what we have for us.
We have the star card, okay, the star.
This is some Aquarian energy,
and I know I have some Aquarius,
and a lot of people might have
checked your placement for Aquarius,
but the star card is like, make a wish card,
a wish coming true, good things happening.
Also, you've got a lot of star power, a lot of energy lately.
Okay, what's the agenda today, it's Saturday, Himea.
What else have we got?
Oh, we have the sun and the star.
Oh, this thing almost the same person too.
We got this blonde.
Or an indiv, anybody blotted to go, go and blub with the sun in the star and the sun is a kind of a star too
So maybe it's talking about the sun, right?
And the sun is all positive things too. It's all, it's all good things
It's one of the most positive cards for the deck. If not the most positive card in the deck, okay?
Okay, hi, he-man
So really got that firepower going, right?
And we got the three of wands. Okay, the three of wands
is a coming together of like, you know, of three.
It's like a kind of like protecting you, guarding you.
It is a once, it is some kind of passion stirring up.
It could be a third party too.
Threes are usually a third party or something like that.
Okay, so you might want to watch out for that,
but I think it's a third party deposit away.
Some people looking out for you.
And we got a six of wands and so yeah, here they all are there are there's a lot of people actually yeah, those are the wands
They'll all the people will start coming out if you need them, right?
I don't feel that's an attack. I feel that's a victory. That's kind of victory for you coming, okay?
And then we have the higher fit and this is kind of led by this higher power
This one looks very lily with a a couple of the owls. I don't know if those are the screech owls, but that's very
with the black hair and the
Now I think Lilith is a connection to the divine.
Finally, we have this eight of wands
and so there's gonna be some kind of really fast moving news
maybe from that higher authority,
maybe some communication coming through.
So listen up for that, okay?
Yep.
Yes.
Do I have advice for the chat?
What's the advice part today?
It's gonna be this one.
10 of wands the advice is like not to you know
It's like there's a lot of energy activity don't get too overwhelmed be careful of taking on other burdens and know that you can
Stand up to any of them even if you feel like you know you're carrying a lot
You can handle this. Okay, but don't at the same time knowing to carry everyone's burden
And then we have this Nine of Pentacles, right?
This is just abundance around you and joy in the world.
You have plenty for not only yourself
for everybody, right?
Hey Summer, how are you?
So that's that reading.
Hope you enjoyed that one.
Hi.
Yeah, so anybody else would like a few cards
or anything like that, you got it?
Yeah, and letting things go.
Yeah, because that that kind of wants is like, you know, usually about caring a lot of burdens
It may feel like she's like oh, she looks maybe almost she doesn't look overwhelmed. She just looks like determined, right?
She's like an it. She's it. She's gonna deal with all of them, right?
Yeah, good to see you summer. I
Had a few naps this morning. Yeah. Oh, yeah, if you naps in there, you know a good morning
I still have my there
It was nice. Oh, thank you. Yeah, I'd like these cards. This is the cat full spider's deck. It's a Christina Ricci design deck. It's really cool
Yeah, I hope you enjoyed the collectives
If anyone wants some cards, I got you yeah
Who is is anybody here last night when it was just like, you know, I got Edward bombs pretty badly, you know, it was like
I was too slow to I knew and it's like I was on my
Amazon fire tablet, which is slow. And so it's like on this tablet
I can get it off in a second, but the Amazon one should had these last night because I didn't have my
Stuff plugged in and so my tablet was the tablet was dead
And my other tablet doesn't work half the time either. It's not charging right now. I
Just don't know
What happened is that the guy was backstage
And I was like, I looked at the name.
It was a male, a man's name.
And then when you clicked on the name,
it has, oh shit, my air just opened up.
You click on the name, the name backstage
was Amanda Hugging Kiss.
If anyone sees that Amanda Hugging Kiss,
that's a porn bomber.
I think it's another one of Tony's.
And just in general, if it's like a name like that,
like I should have just known, and I had a feeling
and I was like, but he was backstage for a long time,
just begging for a reading backstage.
And I was like, oh, I was like, and I told everyone,
I was like, it's probably gonna be a Enver bomb
or a form bomb.
But I'll just take a chance and I did and,
so it didn't pay off, I had to delete it, right?
Yeah, for what it's not for any reason. It's like just it's just Tony trying to harass harass me ruin the show
Have me end the show
See more butts. I mean it had some people with his, you know, dumb names in the chat before but usually they
Weren't weren't that bad, but
Okay, so
Yeah, I mean it's like I shouldn't yeah, it's really it's gonna be old. Yep. What's that noise? I mean n word bomb is being old, too
Oh
You can't knock it over some stuff
I'm going live less now
because
it's
Like the slandering the bullying
the
Just constant harassment the being accused of being a scammer
Just like mean people in a chat even like some friends like you know laughing at me, you know and so
And he's not yeah, he's never gonna give it up. Yeah, it was just it gets to tell by the voice when he was like
Just saying the n-word. He said it probably like ten times
Which is like even if they got it down, it's probably bad for the algorithm
Yeah, I can't I'm it's like the negativity is like I'm sensitive to negativity
And so, you know, it's like people just can use that to their advantage like in you know
Also on on tiktok like no like I can be on YouTube for like hours
and I'll get like maybe at the most 20 likes
and then I now I have access to see the dislikes
and stuff like that and there's a size
with a little amount of just more than normal people,
like normally people would get,
it's just like people come here every day
just to dislike it and then on TikTok,
I go there and it's like,
I'm just doing readings. I'm like doing fast readings and everyone's nice to me
I don't think anyone I don't think I've had one troll there like all those episodes I've done
And then it's like the likes even though, you know, you can like multiple times. I get like
868 10,000 likes I've gotten before and that's like
People are just like sitting there. Tap like they they like me
so
Yeah
Like yesterday
On a beat his show and I'm not saying get it anything but she's just picked up Arthur's call and Arthur's like
Oh, what psyche has no people in in the chat anymore. What's really what's wrong?
Oh, it's because he's such a grifter and then she like she kind of laughed at that and it's like, okay
Well, you know my friends are thinking like laughing like that and I'm not defending me or they're like
That's it. It's the enemies all excited and
Then everybody else is like, oh, she doesn't fuck with him.
Like then he must be a bad person or must be true or whatever.
I would love, no matter what people say,
I'll defend people about what bad people say about them.
Sometimes they get said on my show,
which is like regrettable.
I think it sometimes says more about them
than it does about the person they're saying that about.
But yeah, maybe I have been slow to like kick people off
immediately when I say that or, but.
And it's not all about money.
It's not all about money, but it is about respect.
And I do feel like it's okay if people say shit about me
and personal thing.
They don't like me, but it's like,
I take my business seriously.
And it's like, it is, this thing is my business,
my page, my, you know, my, my pentacle,
my child is trying to grow it.
And it's like,
It's like people attacking your baby kind of thing.
It's like you take it more personally
than they're attacking yourself.
So once you have an ugly baby,
you're gonna get maybe upset
because it's not saying anything about you.
It's a reflection of you kind of.
And then it's like, I don't know.
I don't know if I'm explaining it.
You love mean people, they're always triggered.
Yeah.
Well.
I mean I mean people yeah, and then trolls will say oh you're so triggered
I'm like no you're triggered because you keep repeat you keep saying like last night Stig came in and was just like I was like
Okay, well, I'll let you on piano like whatever it's like
I don't dislike you. I'm not mad at you and then he started saying well
You arbitrarily enforced the rules and you don't get to make the rules YouTube gets to make the rules and YouTube doesn't have this rule
I'm like well, I can make any rule. I want I
I can make YouTube rules, I can follow YouTube rules,
and I can make my own rules, because it's my chat.
And he's like, no, you can't.
And I'm like, I'm not gonna argue about it.
That's just how it is.
I can make the rules.
I'm God here, basically.
And he's like, no, you can't.
So I finally just like banned him permanently
and he's not welcome on the panel or the chat anymore.
I'm just sick of it.
Because I told him to stop arguing with me about it.
And he wouldn't.
He just kept going on and on.
And then he kept going on other accounts
saying the same shit.
It's like I just don't feel like
Continuing really having to explain myself. Just like what I say will go on the show or else
I just won't do the show if like I can't like
even like run it like I want to and I can it's like
So, I don't know hi evil Ron McDonald's
I'm trying to I'm trying to but it's like and so I just like I love like 90% of people out here
I love it's like
And then it's like just like last night it was just like
Having that happen and then just like lead it like deleting another live like it did you know the lead
It was a good live to you were having just fun and just like just chatting and there was you know
People arguing just and it's an end of things. It just stops things
I used to like restart and stuff like that and then it's like
Now I don't even feeling like restarting. I was just like whatever
It's like it kind of feels
I don't feel hopeful. I really do want to continue doing panels and I was like, okay
I'll do all the open panels and like let people on take the risk if I get sponsored this up and that's like
You know everyone said I'm trying to like scam people are charging everyone to come on the panel when it's like
Actually, it's worked fine for me,
so I don't have anything wrong with the program.
But I don't know, it's like,
they want to make it seem like I'm so greedy, selfish,
money hungry, I don't care about anything,
it's that money and dick and that's like the narrative
and it hurts my feelings, but you know,
because it's not true.
It's like pretty much the opposite of what's true, but.
That's like the running
You know, it's just like that. It's like I can't keep defending myself about it
Because it's just like I just but I'll put people who will continue to attack me about it
And then if I don't defend myself, it looks bad. I do defend myself. It looks bad. So I can't win. It's just like
so
you know
But it's not even enough like the numbers are fine. That's fine. I mean, it's like five 22 people
I mean, there's other people, you know, be the head like a hundred people all all day
They know for like to 24 hours or whatever she streamed and you know, I'm just like this little like
Here with like 10 people, you know 15 people and it's like
But I'm fine
Yeah, and I don't want I know it's like it's just like it sounds like I'm just complaining and so so it's like I just won't even
continue to
You could just go out on my ears, right?
My uh, you know, I use AI I don't say hey, I
Made all this myself. I did all the instruments. I wrote all the way. Do I ever say that? No, but it's like I do
input like a lot of information and it's to get the
The lyrics, you know, and I yeah, it's like I don't know how to play instruments
I wouldn't be able to produce them otherwise. And so why is it a big deal? I don't understand and you know that
AI is used by
Professional musicians too. It's like, you know, usually there's some kind of effect or something put on the voice
Like what we hear produced is not necessarily just like the raw thing. It's less like, you know, the higher
Musicians coming in and blah blah blah. It would cost like a million dollars, right?
To produce something so I have an alternative. I can make use of the AI and it comes out with
Interesting funny results. I don't understand why I get so like and then it's like
Is everybody criticized for I mean it's like I just I never heard other people criticize for using it
So I don't understand why it's such a big deal. I do right
It was a joke getting around that I'm a biscuit hater. Oh, yeah, I'm here. Yeah, and it's like
The biscuit thing I was like, let me just take something very arbitrary that doesn't really bother me
And I'll see if it is used as like a hammer to attack me
Because I like this good and I I've seen that super biscuits on I just but I was like
I don't want I didn't want to play it on my show one night because I don't like music being played another YouTube channels on my show, right?
So I was like so and then it's like we just relentlessly jokes about biscuits and it's like
Okay, well, it didn't really bother me.
I just kind of pretended it did
to see if it would be used to attack me,
and it is, and so,
yeah, I mean, so if I don't have a sense of humor
about some things, it's just because it's like,
if some things are like just been used to attack me,
I don't find those things very funny,
and like, or to get a bad reaction or something like that,
but I don't mean to be like so.
humorless about it, but
Just that particular thing was just like a test to see if I like say something bothers me
Am I gonna be constantly attacked with it? But even my friends and yeah
So yeah, I'm out of pot too
Am I talking about the AIDS jokes?
No.
Those are another thing that it's like all of a sudden
people start coming in.
Oh, some lady called in.
Oh, I noticed you have facial, what's it called?
She has your facial something, your facial destruction
of your facial fat.
I forgot what the term was.
She has your facial something.
She's like, is that from your HIV medication?
It's just really offensive.
Well, no, I don't have HIV.
I've always been, I mean, it's like, oh, then I'm on drugs
and then I'm this and that and good times
that everyone's just laughing along with good times.
Oh, you know, it's like, and that gives somebody
like good times who's just like some kind of like asshole
that he finds, oh, I can get attention
by making fun of psyche.
And it's like, you know, and then people will laugh
because, you know, he's just turned into like a big joke,
right?
No one depends me
Facial use it is facial. Oh, it was like not facial stores. It was like facial like
deterioration or something like that or like the
Facial the the fat of my face is deteriorate or something like that. It was just like some kind of dumb
HIV thing, but it was like but then it started happening a lot and it's like
So anyway
Canada dry. I don't know. I don't know. He doesn't he's not funny. I go. I don't know. I don't know his kind of I
Keep giving him chances to
Constantly disappointed some people's personalities just changed you because it's like some people were so cool
Like I liked him a lot like
Never really had a problem with them
He just turned into like some smug asshole
And then I was like talking the other day it's like about like my certain theories about the news media and like how like a lot
Of stories are just psyops, and he's there. Oh really tell me more. Oh, what? Oh my gosh. So interesting
You just talking a sarcastic thing. It's either fine
Lost my teeth like what's your problem?
Yeah
Who's on the shit list? Um, well, you know
Don't even know who everybody is you know because people can have different names and it's like of course
They'll come troll worse on other names. They have voice changers
But he's on a shit list, you know
big
Anybody I've had to kick off multiple times, you know, which is like a lot of people
I'm getting kind of
weary
Continually like letting people up
It's just I have a forgiving nature like even sick
I promise to kick them off the show a hundred times like not even lying a hundred times
I must have like kicked him off the show and
It's like he's like oh if you don't like me just say it and so I'm not welcome on the show
And I'm like well, it's not that I don't like you. It's just like you keep coming on and
just
Either harping on me or like criticizing me. You don't have anything interesting to say you're seeing that and it's like and so
If I can't have a normal conversation, I say I keep wanting to try to do and then he couldn't then he has to start criticizing again
from the chat, so I don't feel like having money feel like if I keep
Giving him chances and stuff. It's like eventually like I shouldn't
Keep giving chances because that just let's everyone know. Oh, you can do you can get away with whatever you want over there
And he'll just you know keep having you on it's like, you know, I know everybody else might might kick you off
But he's like the one person that will like, you know, he's nice enough to like keep letting people on
Because he doesn't hate I don't hate anybody I
Don't hate anybody and they're not one person in the world. I hate like I can see like people have
Problems and they might have traumas and other issues. They might have mental issues and things like that. And so I'm a little bit
sympathetic or empathetic or you know, I
I'd like to be given second chances sometimes I'm never given second chances when Emma wanted me gone
There wasn't even a conversation. I wasn't even able to defend myself. She just you know
Stop talking to me
Block me block my name in her chat. I
Apologize like a thousand times and it was just like oh well. He's harassing me on Instagram. I didn't see that Instagram
I just I sent her one thing. I said, I'm sorry. Can you please don't block me? That's all I said
I wasn't harassing her. I said that one comment
So she's like that's apparently stalking her over social media because I was already you know connected to her on Instagram
But whatever
but maybe I should just be like as mean as her and
Like just nobody gets anything you know, she's her shows fine
She doesn't get attacked form bombed her chat behaves itself or her bonds are like pretty good
Like pretty good with like getting every other really little thing. They're pretty good at getting all my accounts banned
I mean, I wasn't even really doing anything
Just saying saying hi in her chat
I don't know Jimmy. I don't know Jimmy. I mean, it's like I've just been on his snow
I've been on his show one time
Then he was on my show one time both times he took off his shirt and like everyone was laughing and stuff like that
I don't know if I was being used as like to
To do that or something. I don't I don't know. I have nothing against him
He won't come on the show anymore because he's been harassed or some things were coming on the show or he thinks he'll be harassed or something or
But yeah, so he won't come on the show, but I have nothing against the first idol
I just don't know him, you know, it's like a people people try to make these decisions for me
Oh, you're allowed to talk to this person. You're not allowed to talk to this person, you know
We're kicking down your show blah blah blah, right?
Meanwhile the show is the show is still up and
Then people are like, oh, this is why your show got
Taken down the show has never taken down. I had I was false flagged and then I
Was back
Then the fault everything was taken down. I mean everything was taken off, you know, so I'm fine. I'm absolutely fine
You feel like cooking somewhere that sounds
Sounds good at a home cook meal. I had a really good dinner last night. It's a couple lamb euros
what else, French fries, and Turkish coffee.
The Turkish coffee was kind of disappointing
because it's like, you know, I like a strong coffee.
Like a strong coffee.
So it came, the Turkish coffee came in,
I have the cup still, no, I don't.
Okay, but it was in a regular cup
and it was like filled this much.
I know it's stronger, but it was like,
honestly, I don't want like two shots of coffee.
I'd like, you know, I'd rather have like a full thing.
Have like the full, I want a cup of mud.
I would drink a cup of mud.
So I
Know summer summer it gets me down sometimes though because it's like especially
Like it was like my intention. I'm not like a mean person. I think I came on here trying to be
Not trying to be nice. I just am nice. I am like
People take advantage of that though, you know, and it's like I don't want to be not nice
I don't want it to change me into like a mean person and
Sometimes I feel like it gets me
Out of my
Positive energy my good my like good element
Then in turn it's like that. I don't want to spread negative energy to people or like, you know
my own
stuff to people but
The thank you
Yeah
But there's a lot of people that is like oh, I don't go over there anymore because of the because of that because of that because of that
And it's like well the like what the reasons there that they're saying are not even true. I mean, it's these are just things people say
They keep it. It's not things that are untrue. That's what's annoying. It's like and it's not about me
It's okay if you can say anything. I was fine with the fish taco jokes. I'll play into the keys the some of the stupid
jokes and no
I do clown sometimes, and it's like, you know,
it's like, then it gets like,
it starts making like what's supposed to be funny
and like, you know, joyful and like just joke.
It turns it into like some kind of like personality defect
I have or some kind of like, I'm, I'm always,
they're talking about you, you're doing something right.
So just ignore them.
I get talked about all the time.
okay yeah I know I know that there are people that are criticized and it's
like but I feel like I get it pretty bad I don't I've seen people and people get
it bad too I mean when I was watching Bita when she started like I guess you
would get poor and bomb continuously like you know a lot I was like wow what's
that about like I I guess it's like some of the some of the trolling
I know the honestly that the person sat back up for half hour. I'm like, well, if he's like sad back there half hour
Obviously, maybe he does want to read you because it's like who wants to sit who wants to really porn bomb that bad?
But yeah, this guy does
Or and we're bomb
Yeah
And yeah in the mod mods, you know, if I want someone hidden which I've been wanting more people hidden lately because I just like had enough
Then I'll let I'll ask once can you hide the person but usually I'll just do it myself
And I appreciate if mods if I don't say anything about something and I miss something either bring it to my attention or
Time them out for an appropriate
Minutes but it's like there's certain things that there's like zero tolerance if it gets into like racial stuff it gets into doxing
if it gets into
slander
Or if it's just like rude
in the cruel or
I'm down to hide those people
Because those come on different accounts
So it's like almost not even like but at least like
Like say just kept giving himself away like so just continue to
ban their accounts
Eventually we'll get all of them because it's like it's not like you can make unlimited accounts. I mean I've tried right I
Only have like 10
You were gay dog off to go look at the list again. I mean, I don't know. I don't know why I
Have to check my band words make sure that they're not being tampered with by managing mods like because sometimes like I've had that happen
Really annoying
Right
Yeah, the celebrities. Yeah, but it's like celebrities have really, you know
On the other hand they have so many people that like love them and talk well about them
I don't get I don't I don't see when I go to other shows
It's like if I'm being talked about somewhere 90% of the time. It's in a really negative context
Like I see other people. Oh, I love her. I love her. I love her. Oh, she's great. Oh, I love her. She's perfect
You know, he's all I love him and it's just like for me. It's like, oh, do you see what he's doing that?
Like, oh, look at it. It's just like so negative about me
Hmm
Your last word about you multiple times a day you're gonna be over that. Yeah
Yeah
Yeah, poor mom every show. Okay
Thank you summer. Thank you. You're amazing too
Well, that's what keeps me. That's what does keep me here and I still have gone
Maybe I've done a little bit less and I've been really tired lately and stuff
a little bit worn out, but um
And I will be back, you know
Longer shows and stuff
It's just and I've been but I have been doing it every day
But it's like if I keep getting poor moms. I just like
I'll go to like a friendlier place
like I
Don't know. I don't think they have I've never seen anybody get formed on on kick talk
And they do have like, you know people come on and can talk and stuff like that. Thank you summer
Yeah guys
Yeah
Maybe I maybe I will you know, it's like I've been giving people back wrenches and stuff like that that have kind of proven themselves, but
But anyway, I want to show you this thing this is my
Thing I got because I had this little problem with like my my ear's real clogged and so this is a camera on it
You just go in you can see the camera. It's really gross, but when you go in you can see everything
Like my inside of my ears really hairy and there's a big block hitch in there
Sorry if I if I I'm listening to other shows like if I was if I listen to their shows
And I it's always negative. It's like it's never nothing ever positive
It's always negative and I'm sitting right there like, you know, I don't announce myself always
Something and then but then I sometimes I'll say things like I didn't have on your show with random guy was like, oh sec
He's just my bitch. I he'll I own him for the next two months. I
Really don't like the idea of anybody owning anybody also. It's like
A donation is supposed to be done with like love and sometimes for a purpose. It's not to be done to like
try to own
Control or make me up make me your bitch. I mean, it's like it's like that
I mean
So I'm not good. It's not not going to be right
Yeah, well, you know, you can like always hit me up if you are if you are
Blocked or something. I'll always look at the list for people and stuff. So
I'm trying I'm trying
It's like but you know
People I mean it's just like and then it's it's like people are kind of sheep
Sometimes in a way where this like if someone says something then everyone just believes it
It's like and then it's like it's so effective to slander. That's why it's like illegal, right? Because it's effective because it really
Can hurt reputations it hurts which basically hurts the business
Hurts everything like no one
No one even asked for readings here anymore like I did one last night the lady was like so thrilled like she's like
Oh my god, she was this lady in brosa. I loved it. I'm ticked off. I'm getting messages
Oh my god, you told me this and this happened like it's like so I know I'm good
I'm getting the positive feedback that it's like nobody wants to
I don't know.
But yeah, I did come to play this song and stuff like that.
So I'll play this song one more time and then I'll be back later.
But thank you guys for being here. Love you guys. Hope you had a fun day.
Here's the new song again.
I'll see you later.
Rockies in his Speedos, Stars and Stripes Parade
Fish tacos on the table, Another wild charade
He's hitting on the straight men, Come on, lose that shirt
Meanwhile, beatas on the hotline, Yelling till it hurts
Pretty pages dodging simps, Like dodgeball in-
Christine's with Fawzi Bear
Arthur's stirring pots like he's cooking up a scare
Trucker Rattle rumbles in
Sam is chasing views DJ
Electra's cartoon face